Guide to the Vassar College Photograph Files, approximately 1865-2014
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- V. C. Faculty
  Note: For faculty before circa 1890, see also: faculty photograph album in the Frances Wood Papers.
  - V. C. Faculty - A-Ap (Folder 6.10)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ar-Au (Folder 6.11)
  - V. C. Faculty - Av-Az (Folder 6.12)
  - V. C. Faculty - Bab-Bal (Folder 6.13)
  - V. C. Faculty - Bar-Bau (Folder 6.14)
  - V. C. Faculty - Bea-Bel (Folder 6.15)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ben-Bey (Folder 6.16)
  - V. C. Faculty - Bergeret, Ida Treat (OV3.021)
  - V. C. Faculty - Blanding, Sarah Gibson (Folder 6.17-6.20)
  - V. C. Faculty - Blanding, Sarah Gibson (OV3.022)
  - V. C. Faculty - Bun-Bra (Folder 6.21)
  - V. C. Faculty - Braislin, Priscilla H. (Folder 6.22)
  - V. C. Faculty - Bri-Bro (Folder 6.23)
  - V. C. Faculty - Bru-But (Folder 6.24)
  - V. C. Faculty - Caldwell, Samuel L. (Folder 6.25)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ca-Chan (Folder 6.26)
  - V. C. Faculty - Chap-Chu (Folder 6.27)
  - V. C. Faculty - Miss Chittenden (OV1.082)
  - V. C. Faculty - Miss Chittenden (birthday dinner) (OV3.025)
  - V. C. Faculty - Christie, John Alrich (OV1.072)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ci-Con (Folder 6.28)
  - V. C. Faculty - Clark, Evalyn (OV2.041)
  - V. C. Faculty - Cooley, LeRoy C. (Folder 6.29)
  - V. C. Faculty - Cooley, LeRoy C. (OV2.034)
  - V. C. Faculty - Coo-Cu (Folder 6.30)
  - V. C. Faculty - Crawford, Marjorie (OV2.035)
  - V. C. Faculty - Da (Folder 6.31)
  - V. C. Faculty - De (Folder 6.32)
  - V. C. Faculty - Di-Do (Folder 6.33)
  - V. C. Faculty - Martha Doan (OV1.071)
  - V. C. Faculty - Drouillhet, Elizabeth Moffatt (VC 1930) (Folder 6.34)
  - V. C. Faculty - Dr-Dy (Folder 6.35)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ea-Els (Folder 7.1)
  - V. C. Faculty - Elw-Ev (Folder 7.2)
  - V. C. Faculty - Erck, Theodore (OV3.023)
  - V. C. Faculty - Fa-Fe (Folder 7.3)
  - V. C. Faculty - Fi-Fo (Folder 7.4)
  - V. C. Faculty - Fr-Fu (Folder 7.5)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ga-Gde (Folder 7.6)
  - V. C. Faculty - Gi-Gl (Folder 7.7)
  - V. C. Faculty - Go (Folder 7.8)
  - V. C. Faculty - Gould, Miriam (OV1.083)
  - V. C. Faculty - Gow, George C. (OV1.036)
  - V. C. Faculty - Gow, George C. (OV1.073)
  - V. C. Faculty - Gr-Gu (Folder 7.9)
  - V. C. Faculty - Griffin, Carroll (OV3.024)
  - V. C. Faculty - Haa-Har (Folder 7.10)
  - V. C. Faculty - Has-Hen (Folder 7.11)
  - V. C. Faculty - Her-Hil (Folder 7.12)
  - V. C. Faculty - Hin-Hod (Folder 7.13)
  - V. C. Faculty - Hol-Hud (Folder 7.14)
  - V. C. Faculty - Hum-Je (Folder 7.15)
  - V. C. Faculty - Jo-Ju (Folder 7.16)
  - V. C. Faculty - Johnson, Colton (OV1.084)
  - V. C. Faculty - Judson, Margaret (OV1.085)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ka (Folder 7.17)
  - V. C. Faculty - Katzenellenbogen, Adolf (OV3.026)
  - V. C. Faculty - Kayden, Mildred Goldstein (OV3.027)
  - V. C. Faculty - Kel-Kem (Folder 7.18)
  - V. C. Faculty - Kendrick, J. Ryland & Georgia Avery (OV2.037)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ken-Ker (Folder 7.19)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ki-Kn (Folder 7.20)
  - V. C. Faculty - Knapp, William Ireland (OV1.069)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ko-Ku (Folder 7.21)
  - V. C. Faculty - La (Folder 7.22)
  - V. C. Faculty – Langmuir, Mary Shattuck Fisher (OV3.028)
  - V. C. Faculty - Lea-Lei (Folder 7.23)
  - V. C. Faculty - Leach, Abby (OV2.038)
  - V. C. Faculty - Leo-Lew (Folder 7.24)
  - V. C. Faculty - Li-Ll (Folder 7.25)
  - V. C. Faculty - Lo (Folder 7.26)
  - V. C. Faculty - Lu-Ly (Folder 7.27)
  - V. C. Faculty - Mac (Folder 7.28)
  - V. C. Faculty - Macurdy, Grace H. (OV1.086)
  - V. C. Faculty - Mag-Mal (Folder 7.29)
  - V. C. Faculty - Man-Mar (Folder 7.30)
  - V. C. Faculty - Mas-May (Folder 7.31)
  - V. C. Faculty - McA-McC (Folder 7.32)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ella McCaleb (OV2.039)
  - V. C. Faculty - McD-McN (Folder 7.33)
  - V. C. Faculty -Me (Folder 7.34)
  - V. C. Faculty - Mi (Folder 7.35)
  - V. C. Faculty - Mitchell, Maria [See also: V.C. Departments. Astronomy, and the Archives Files Collection] (Folder 7.36)
  - V. C. Faculty - Mitchell, Maria (OV3.130)
  - V. C. Faculty - Mol-Moo (Folder 7.37)
  - V. C. Faculty - Mora-Morr (Folder 8.1)
  - V. C. Faculty - Mors-My (Folder 8.2)
  - V. C. Faculty - Na-Nev (Folder 8.3)
  - V. C. Faculty - New-Nk (Folder 8.4)
  - V. C. Faculty - Noc-Nov (Folder 8.5)
  - V. C. Faculty - O-Om (Folder 8.6)
  - V. C. Faculty - Nor-Nov (Folder 8.7)
  - V. C. Faculty - Orton, James (Folder 8.8)
  - V. C. Faculty - Os-Pal (Folder 8.9)
  - V. C. Faculty - Pam-Pat (Folder 8.10)
  - V. C. Faculty - Parrish, Carl (OV1.217)
  - V. C. Faculty - Pau-Pea (Folder 8.11)
  - V. C. Faculty - Pec-Pen (Folder 8.12)
  - V. C. Faculty - Per (Folder 8.13)
  - V. C. Faculty - Pet-Ph (Folder 8.14)
  - V. C. Faculty - Pi (Folder 8.15)
  - V. C. Faculty - Pl (Folder 8.16)
  - V. C. Faculty - Poi-Pol (Folder 8.17)
  - V. C. Faculty - Pom-Por (Folder 8.18)
  - V. C. Faculty - Pos-Pow (Folder 8.19)
  - V. C. Faculty - Post, Charles (OV1.087)
  - V. C. Faculty - Powell, Elizabeth (OV2.040)
  - V. C. Faculty - Pratt, Charles Millard (Folder 8.20)
  - V. C. Faculty - Pr-Q (Folder 8.21)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ra (Folder 8.22)
  - V. C. Faculty - Raymond, Cornelia M. (Folder 8.23)
  - V. C. Faculty - Raymond, John Howard (Folders 8.24-8.25)
  - V. C. Faculty - Raymond, John Howard (OV3.136)
  - V. C. Faculty - Reed (Folder 8.26)
  - V. C. Faculty - Reg-Rey (Folder 8.27)
  - V. C. Faculty - Reynolds (Folder 8.28)
  - V. C. Faculty - Rice-Richards (Folder 8.29)
  - V. C. Faculty - Richards, Elizabeth M. (OV3.029)
  - V. C. Faculty - Richardson-Richter (Folder 8.30)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ril-Rip (Folder 8.31)
  - V. C. Faculty - Rit (Folder 8.32)
  - V. C. Faculty - Roa-Rom (Folder 8.33)
  - V. C. Faculty - Roosevelt (Folder 8.34)
  - V. C. Faculty - Rosa-Rose (Folder 8.35)
  - V. C. Faculty - Rosen-Ross (Folder 8.36)
  - V. C. Faculty - Rot-Rua (Folder 8.37)
  - V. C. Faculty - Rub-Russ (Folder 8.38)
  - V. C. Faculty - Russo-Ry (Folder 8.39)
  - V. C. Faculty - Sa-Sal (Folder 8.40)
  - V. C. Faculty - Salmon, Lucy Maynard [missing as of Oct 2004] (OV?)
  - V. C. Faculty - San-Sau (Folder 8.41)
  - V. C. Faculty - Sav-Sca (Folder 8.42)
  - V. C. Faculty - Sch (Folder 8.43)
  - V. C. Faculty - Sco-Sea (Folder 8.44)
  - V. C. Faculty - Sec-Sey (Folder 8.45)
  - V. C. Faculty - Sh (Folder 8.46)
  - V. C. Faculty - Simpson, Alan (Folders 8.47-8.50)
  - V. C. Faculty - Simpson, Alan (OV1.088)
  - V. C. Faculty - Simpson, Alan (OV3.131)
  - V. C. Faculty - Sin-Sl (Folder 8.51)
  - V. C. Faculty - Smith, G. - Smith, K. (Folder 8.52)
  - V. C. Faculty - Smith, M. - Smith, W. (Folder 8.53)
  - V. C. Faculty - Smith, Virginia B. (Folder 8.54)
  - V. C. Faculty - Spo (Folder 8.55)
  - V. C. Faculty - Sp (Folder 8.56)
  - V. C. Faculty - Sta-Stec (Folder 8.57)
  - V. C. Faculty - Sted-Stem (Folder 8.58)
  - V. C. Faculty - Step-Stev (Folder 8.59)
  - V. C. Faculty - Stewart (Folder 8.60)
  - V. C. Faculty - Sti (Folder 8.61)
  - V. C. Faculty - Sto (Folder 8.62)
  - V. C. Faculty - Stre (Folder 8.63)
  - V. C. Faculty - Stro (Folder 8.64)
  - V. C. Faculty - Su (Folder 8.65)
  - V. C. Faculty - Swa (Folder 8.66)
  - V. C. Faculty - Swe-Swi (Folder 8.67)
  - V. C. Faculty - Tait, Marion (Folder 8.68)
  - V. C. Faculty - Tait, Marion (OV1.089)
  - V. C. Faculty - Tap-Tav (Folder 8.69)
  - V. C. Faculty - Taylor (Folder 8.70)
  - V. C. Faculty - Taylor, James Monroe (Folder 8.70a)
  - V. C. Faculty - Taylor, James Monroe (OV1.070)
  - V. C. Faculty - Taylor, James Monroe (OV2.042)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ten (Folder 8.71)
  - V. C. Faculty - Terry, Harriet W. (Folder 8.72)
  - V. C. Faculty - Tha (Folder 8.73)
  - V. C. Faculty - Thelberg, Elizabeth Burr (Folder 8.74)
  - V. C. Faculty - Thomas-Thompson (Folder 8.75)
  - V. C. Faculty - Thompson, Frederick Ferris (OV2.043)
  - V. C. Faculty - Thompson, Frederick Ferris (OV3.137)
  - V. C. Faculty - Thompson, Mary Clark (OV1.090)
  - V. C. Faculty - Thomson, Vera Baton (Folder 8.76)
  - V. C. Faculty - Thornbury, Zita L. (Folder 8.77)
  - V. C. Faculty - Thorn-Ti (Folder 8.78)
  - V. C. Faculty - Thornton, Eileen (OV2.044)
  - V. C. Faculty - To (Folder 8.79)
  - V. C. Faculty - Tra-Trea (Folder 8.80)
  - V. C. Faculty - Tre-Tri (Folder 8.81)
  - V. C. Faculty - Tu-U (Folder 8.82)
  - V. C. Faculty - Val-Vander (Folder 8.83)
  - V. C. Faculty - Van De W. - Van V. (Folder 8.84)
  - V. C. Faculty - Van Ingen, Henry (Folder 8.85)
  - V. C. Faculty - Van Ingen, Henry (OV2.045)
  - V. C. Faculty - Vassar John Guy (Folder 8.86)
  - V. C. Faculty - Vassar, Matthew [and Matthew Vassar, Jr.?] (Folder 8.87)
  - V. C. Faculty - Vassar, Matthew (stereopticon) (Odd formats box)
  - V. C. Faculty - Veb-Ven (Folder 8.88)
  - V. C. Faculty - Ver-Von (Folder 8.89)
  - V. C. Faculty - Voo-Wag (Folder 8.90)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wal (Folder 8.91)
  - V. C. Faculty - War (Folder 8.92)
  - V. C. Faculty - Washburn, Margaret Floy (Folder 8.93)
  - V. C. Faculty - Washington-Webster (Folder 8.94)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wee-Wei (Folder 8.95)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wel (Folder 8.96)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wes (Folder 8.97)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wh (Folder 8.98)
  - V. C. Faculty - Whitney, Mary Watson (Folder 8.99)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wick-Wild (Folder 8.100)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wile-Wilk (Folder 8.101)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wil (Folder 8.102)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wilson-Win (Folder 8.103)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wir-Wit (Folder 8.104)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wo (Folder 8.105)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wood, Frances (OV2.120)
  - V. C. Faculty - Woodward, Helen D. (OV1.091)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wr-Y (Folder 8.106)
  - V. C. Faculty - Wylie, Laura (OV1.092)
  - V. C. Faculty - Z (Folder 8.10)
  - V. C. Faculty - Unidentified (Folder 8.10)
  - V. C. Faculty - Unidentified (OV3.030)
  - V. C. Faculty - Unidentified librarian (OV3.059)
- V. C. Faculty Children (Folder 8.109)
- V. C. Faculty Groups (Folder 8.110)
- V. C. Faculty Plays (Folder 8.111)
- V. C. Faculty Plays (OV1.093)
- V. C. Faculty Rooms (Folder 8.112)
- V. C. Field Day [See also: V. C. Students. Athletics] (Folders 9.1-9.2)
- V. C. Field Day (OV1.094)
- V. C. Field Trips (Folder 9.3)
- V. C. Field Work (Folder 9.4)
- V. C. Fire Department (Folder 9.5)
- V. C. Founder's Day. Earlier ones, undated (Folder 9.6)
- V. C. Founder's Day, undated (OV1.095)
- V. C. Founder's Day. 1866, 1911 (45th Anniversary) (Folder 9.7)
- V. C. Founder's Day. 1914 (Folder 9.8)
- V. C. Founder's Day. 1913-1919 (Folder 9.9)
- V. C. Founder's Day. 1920-1929 (Folder 9.10)
- V. C. Founder's Day. 1930-1939 (Folder 9.11)
- V. C. Founder's Day. 1940-1949 (Folder 9.12)
- V. C. Founder's Day. 1950 - and undated 40's and 50's (Folder 9.13)
- V. C. Gavel Ceremony (Folder 9.14)
- V. C. Hoop Rolling (Folder 9.15)
- V. C. Hoop Rolling (OV1.096)
- V. C. House Fellows (Folder 9.16)
- V.C. Ice cutting (Folder 9.16a)
- V. C. Lantern Ceremony, 1940s (Folder 9.17)
- V. C. Lecturers & Visitors. A-B (Folder 9.18)
- V. C. Lecturers & Visitors. C-F (Folder 9.19)
- V. C. Lecturers & Visitors. G-K (Folder 9.20)
- V. C. Lecturers & Visitors. L-O (Folder 9.21)
- V. C. Lecturers & Visitors. P-S (Folder 9.22)
- V. C. Lecturers & Visitors. T-Z, unidentified (Folder 9.23)
- V. C. May-pole & May Day [See also: V. C. Hoop rolling] (Folder 9.24)
- V. C. May-pole & May Day (OV3.087)
- V. C. May-pole & May Day (OV3.090)
- V. C. May-pole & May Day (OV3.093)
- V. C. Museums (Folder 9.25)
- V. C. Music (Folder 9.26)
- V. C. Nursery School. Photos of children alone [See also: V. C. Buildings. Nursery School; V. C. Departments. Child Study] (Folders 9.27-9.29)
- V. C. Nursery School. Photos of children alone (OV1.097)
- V. C. Nursery School. Adult with child (OV1.220)
- V. C. Opening of College (Folder 9.30)
- V. C. Outdoor Classes (Folder 9.31)
- V. C. Parents' Weekend [See: V. C. Sophomore Fathers' Weekend]
- V. C. Phi Beta Kappa Chapter (Folder 9.32)
- V. C. Physicians (Folder 9.33)
- V. C. Presidents (Folder 9.34)
- V. C. Renaissance Colloquium (Folder 9.35)
- V. C. Salary Endowment Fund (Folder 9.36)
- V. C. Salve Night (Folder 9.37)
- V. C. Senior Auction (Folder 9.38)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1875-1880 (Folder 9.39)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1877 (OV1.098)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1881-1885 (Folder 9.40)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1882 (OV3.066)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, [1884?] (OV1.218)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1886-1888 (Folder 9.41)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1889-1892 (Folder 9.42)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1893-1896 (Folder 9.43)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1897-1899 (Folder 9.44)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1897 (OV2.046)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1899 (OV1.219)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1900-1910 (Folder 9.45)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1911-1915 (Folder 9.46)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1916-1920 (Folder 9.47)
- V. C. Senior Parlor, 1921-1932, undated (Folder 9.48)
- V. C. Social Museum (in Blodgett), 1937 October 3 (Folder 9.49)
- V. C. Sophomore Fathers' Weekend (Folder 9.50)
- V. C. Student Government (Folder 9.51)
- V. C. Student Rooms (early), undated (Folder 9.52)
- V. C. Student Rooms (early), undated (OV1.099)
- V. C. Student Rooms, 1870s-1880s (Folder 9.53)
- V. C. Student Rooms, circa 1878 (OV1.208)
- V. C. Student Rooms, 1890-1899 (Folder 10.1)
- V. C. Student Rooms, circa 1900-1939 (Folder 10.2)
- V. C. Student Rooms, 1940-1949 (Folder 10.3)
- V. C. Student Rooms, 1950-1959 (Folder 10.4)
- V. C. Student Rooms, 1960-1969 (Folder 10.5)
- V. C. Student Rooms, 1970-1979 (Folder 10.6)
- V. C. Student Rooms, 1980-1989 (Folder 10.7)
- V. C. Student Rooms, undated (Folder 10.8)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1865-1911 (Baseball - Fencing) (Folder 10.9a)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1865-1911 (Basketball) (Folder 10.9b)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1865-1911 (Basketball) (Folder 10.9c)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1865-1911 (Field Hockey - Track & misc.) (Folder 10.10)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1885-1907. (Basketball & Hockey) (OV1.100)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1885-1907. (Basketball & Hockey) (OV2.047)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1885-1907. (Basketball & Hockey) (OV2.048)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1901 (Field Hockey) (OV3.067)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1912-1918 (Folder 10.11)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1919-1928 (Folder 10.12)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1929-1940 (Folder 10.13)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1940 (Field Hockey) (OV3.068)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1941- (Folders 10.14-10.16)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. 1941 - (Bowling and Fencing) (OV2.049)
- V. C. Students. Athletics. Undated (Tennis) (OV2.123)
- V. C. Students. Bicycle Races (Yale-Vassar) (Folder 10.17)
- V. C. Students. Boat Trips (Folder 10.18)
- V. C. Students. Boat Trips (OV1.101)
- V. C. Students. Boating (Folder 10.19)
- V. C. Students. Boating [tintypes], circa 1870-1880 (Odd formats box)
- V. C. Students. Bulletin Boards (Folder 10.20)
- V. C. Students. Card Playing (Folder 10.21)
- V. C. Students. Special and Preparatory Students. Individuals. A-E (Folder 10.22)
- V. C. Students. Special and Preparatory Students. Individuals. A-E (Odd formats box)
- V. C. Students. Special and Preparatory Students. Individuals. F-L (Folder 10.23)
- V. C. Students. Special and Preparatory Students. Individuals. M-S (Folder 10.24)
- V. C. Students. Special and Preparatory Students. Individuals. T-Z (Folder 10.25)
- V. C. Students. Special and Preparatory Students. Individuals. T-Z (Odd formats box)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1867. Individuals (Folder 10.26)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1868. Individuals (Folder 10.26)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1869. Individuals (Folder 10.27)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1869. Wright, Susan (Odd formats box)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1869. Group (OV1.102)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1869. Group (OV3.109)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1870. Individuals (Folder 10.28)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1870. Ellen Richards (OV1.103)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1871. Individuals (Folder 10.29)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1872. Individuals. A-L (Folder 10.30)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1872. Individuals. M-Z (Folder 10.31)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1873. Individuals. A-G (Folder 10.32)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1873. Group: Freshman and/or Senior Year Photos (Folder 10.32)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1873. Group: Freshman and/or Senior Year Photos (OV1.104)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1873. Individuals. H-P (Folder 10.33)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1873. Individuals. R-Z (Folder 10.34)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1874. Individuals. A-H (Folder 10.35)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1874. Individuals. J-Z (Folder 10.36)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1875. Individuals. A-L (Folder 10.37)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1875. Individuals. M-Z (Folder 10.38)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1876. Individuals. A-K (Folder 10.39)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1876. Group (OV1.105)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1876. Heloise & Hersey (OV1.106)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1876. Individuals. L-Z (Folder 10.40)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1877. Individuals. A-Z (pictures on both sides) (Folder 11.1)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1877. Caroline Swift Atwater (OV1.107)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1877. Individuals. A-N (Folder 11.2)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1877. George Lawrence (OV1.108)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1877. Individuals. P-Z (Folder 11.3)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1877. Rouse, Fannie (Odd formats box)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1877. Group (OV1.109)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1878. Individuals. A-D (Folder 11.4)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1878. Individuals. F-R (Folder 11.5)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1878. Individuals. S-Z (Folder 11.6)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1879 (OV1.110)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1879. Individuals. A-C (Folder 11.7)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1879. Individuals. D-M (Folder 11.8)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1879. Individuals. N-Z (Folder 11.9)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1879. Small Misc. Groups (Folder 11.9)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1880 (OV2.050)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1880. Individuals. A-H (Folder 11.10)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1880. Individuals. J-Z (Folder 11.11)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1881 (OV2.051)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1881. Individuals. A-D (Folder 11.12)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1881. Individuals. E-M (Folder 11.13)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1881. Individuals. N-Z (Folder 11.14)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1881. Small Misc. Groups (Folder 11.14)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1882 (OV1.111)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1882 (OV2.052)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1882. Individuals. A-R (Folder 11.15)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1882. Individuals. S-Z, unidentified (Folder 11.16)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1883 (OV1.112)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1883 (OV2.053)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1883. Individuals. A-O (Folder 11.17)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1883. Individuals. P-Z (Folder 11.18)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1884 (OV2.054)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1884. Individuals. A-H (Folder 11.19)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1884. Individuals. J-Z (Folder 11.20)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1885 (OV1.113)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1885 (OV2.055)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1885. Individuals. (Folder 11.21)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1886. (OV1.209)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1886. Individuals. (Folder 11.22)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1886. Ada Fox (OV1.114)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1887 (OV1.115)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1887. Individuals. A-L (Folder 11.23)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1887. Individuals. M-Z (Folder 11.24)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1888 (OV1.116)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1888 (OV2.056)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1888. Individuals. A-O (Folder 11.25)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1888. Small groups (Folder 11.25)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1888. Individuals. P-Z (Folder 11.26)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1889. Individuals. A-I (Folder 11.27)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1889. Lola Iddings (OV1.117)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1889. Individuals. J-Z (Folder 11.28)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1889. Small groups (Folder 11.28)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1889. Group (OV1.118)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1889. Group (OV1.119)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1890. Individuals. A-L (Folder 11.29)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1890. Emma B. Hart (OV1.120)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1890. Individuals. M-Z (Folder 11.30)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1890. Group (OV1.121-OV1.122)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1891 (OV1.123-OV1.124)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1891. Individuals. A-M (Folder 11.31)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1891. Small groups (Folder 11.31)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1891. Individuals. N-Z (Folder 11.32)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1892 (OV1.125-OV1.126)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1892. Group. First-year portrait, 1888 (Framed Storage 1.7)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1892. Individuals. A-M (Folder 11.33)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1892. Individuals. N-Z (Folder 11.34)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1893 (OV1.127-OV1.128)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1893. Individuals. (Folder 11.35)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1894 (OV1.129)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1894. Individuals. A-F (Folder 11.36)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1894. Lucy Fitch (OV1.130)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1894. Individuals. G-R (Folder 11.37)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1894. Individuals. S-Z (Folder 11.38)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1895 (OV1.131)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1895 (OV2.057)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1895. Individuals. A-L (Folder 11.39)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1895. Individuals. M-T (Folder 11.40)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1895. Individuals. U-Z, unidentified (Folder 11.41)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1895. Small groups (Folder 11.41)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1896 (OV1.132-OV1.133)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1896. Individuals. A-B (Folder 12.1)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1896. Individuals. C-D (Folder 12.2)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1896. Individuals. E-H (Folder 12.3)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1896. Individuals. I-L (Folder 12.4)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1896. Individuals. M-N (Folder 12.5)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1896. Individuals. O-S (Folder 12.6)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1896. Individuals. T-Z (Folder 12.7)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1896. Small Misc. Groups (Folder 12.7)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1897. (OV3.069)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1897. (OV3.070)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1897. (OV3.084)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1897. Individuals. A-H (Folder 12.8)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1897. Anita Hemmings (OV3.110)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1897. Individuals. I-Z (Folder 12.9)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1898 (OV2.058)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1898. Individuals. A-H (Folder 12.10)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1898. Lucy Fay (OV1.134)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1898. Individuals. J-Z (Folder 12.11)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1899 (OV1.135)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1899 (OV2.059)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1899. Individuals. A-C (Folder 12.12)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1899. Myra Cook (OV1.136)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1899. Individuals. D-H (Folder 12.13)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1899. Individuals. J-M (Folder 12.14)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1899. Individuals. N-S (Folder 12.15)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1899. Individuals. T-W (Folder 12.16)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1899. Small groups (Folder 12.16)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1900 (OV1.137)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1900 (OV2.060)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1900 (OV3.071-OV3.072)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1900. Individuals (OV1.138)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1900. Individuals. A-B (Folder 12.17)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1900. Individuals. C-J (Folder 12.18)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1900. Individuals. K-P (Folder 12.19)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1900. Individuals. R-Z (Folder 12.20)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1900. Small groups (Folder 12.20)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1901 (OV1.139)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1901 (OV2.061)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1901 (OV3.081)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1901. Individuals. A-B (Folder 12.21)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1901. Individuals. C-F (Folder 12.22)
- V. C. Students. Class of 1901. Individuals. G-J (Folder 12.23)